export const chapter1StudyData = [
  // Key Terms
  {
    id: "KT101",
    front: "American Psychological Association",
    back: "professional organization representing psychologists in the United States"
  },
  {
    id: "KT102",
    front: "behaviorism",
    back: "focus on observing and controlling behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT103",
    front: "biopsychology",
    back: "study of how biology influences behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT104",
    front: "biopsychosocial model",
    back: "perspective that asserts that biology, psychology, and social factors interact to determine an individual's health"
  },
  {
    id: "KT105",
    front: "clinical psychology",
    back: "area of psychology that focuses on the diagnosis and treatment of psychological disorders and other problematic patterns of behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT106",
    front: "cognitive psychology",
    back: "study of cognitions, or thoughts, and their relationship to experiences and actions"
  },
  {
    id: "KT107",
    front: "counseling psychology",
    back: "area of psychology that focuses on improving emotional, social, vocational, and other aspects of the lives of psychologically healthy individuals"
  },
  {
    id: "KT108",
    front: "developmental psychology",
    back: "scientific study of development across a lifespan"
  },
  {
    id: "KT109",
    front: "dissertation",
    back: "long research paper about research that was conducted as a part of the candidate's doctoral training"
  },
  {
    id: "KT110",
    front: "empirical method",
    back: "method for acquiring knowledge based on observation, including experimentation, rather than a method based only on forms of logical argument or previous authorities"
  },
  {
    id: "KT111",
    front: "forensic psychology",
    back: "area of psychology that applies the science and practice of psychology to issues within and related to the justice system"
  },
  {
    id: "KT112",
    front: "functionalism",
    back: "focused on how mental activities helped an organism adapt to its environment"
  },
  {
    id: "KT113",
    front: "humanism",
    back: "perspective within psychology that emphasizes the potential for good that is innate to all humans"
  },
  {
    id: "KT114",
    front: "introspection",
    back: "process by which someone examines their own conscious experience in an attempt to break it into its component parts"
  },
  {
    id: "KT115",
    front: "ology",
    back: "suffix that denotes \"scientific study of\""
  },
  {
    id: "KT116",
    front: "personality psychology",
    back: "study of patterns of thoughts and behaviors that make each individual unique"
  },
  {
    id: "KT117",
    front: "personality trait",
    back: "consistent pattern of thought and behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT118",
    front: "PhD (doctor of philosophy)",
    back: "doctoral degree conferred in many disciplinary perspectives housed in a traditional college of liberal arts and sciences"
  },
  {
    id: "KT119",
    front: "postdoctoral training program",
    back: "allows young scientists to further develop their research programs and broaden their research skills under the supervision of other professionals in the field"
  },
  {
    id: "KT120",
    front: "psyche",
    back: "Greek word for soul"
  },
  {
    id: "KT121",
    front: "psychoanalytic theory",
    back: "focus on the role of the unconscious in affecting conscious behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT122",
    front: "psychology",
    back: "scientific study of the mind and behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT123",
    front: "PsyD (doctor of psychology)",
    back: "doctoral degree that places less emphasis on research-oriented skills and focuses more on application of psychological principles in the clinical context"
  },
  {
    id: "KT124",
    front: "sport and exercise psychology",
    back: "area of psychology that focuses on the interactions between mental and emotional factors and physical performance in sports, exercise, and other activities"
  },
  {
    id: "KT125",
    front: "structuralism",
    back: "understanding the conscious experience through introspection"
  },
  // Review Questions
  {
    id: "R101",
    front: "Which of the following was mentioned as a skill to which psychology students would be exposed?",
    back: "all of the above (critical thinking, use of the scientific method, critical evaluation of sources of information)"
  },
  {
    id: "R102",
    front: "Psyche is a Greek word meaning ________.",
    back: "soul"
  },
  {
    id: "R103",
    front: "Before psychology became a recognized academic discipline, matters of the mind were undertaken by those in ________.",
    back: "philosophy"
  },
  {
    id: "R104",
    front: "In the scientific method, a hypothesis is a(n) ________.",
    back: "proposed explanation"
  },
  {
    id: "R105",
    front: "Based on your reading, which theorist would have been most likely to agree with this statement: Perceptual phenomena are best understood as a combination of their components.",
    back: "Wundt/structuralism"
  },
  {
    id: "R106",
    front: "________ is most well-known for proposing his hierarchy of needs.",
    back: "Abraham Maslow"`
  },
  {
    id: "R107",
    front: "Rogers believed that providing genuineness, empathy, and ________ in the therapeutic environment for his clients was critical to their being able to deal with their problems.",
    back: "unconditional positive regard"
  },
  {
    id: "R108",
    front: "The operant conditioning chamber (aka ________ box) is a device used to study the principles of operant conditioning.",
    back: "Skinner"
  },
  {
    id: "R109",
    front: "A researcher interested in how changes in the cells of the hippocampus (a structure in the brain related to learning and memory) are related to memory formation would be most likely to identify as a(n) ________ psychologist.",
    back: "biological"
  },
  {
    id: "R110",
    front: "An individual's consistent pattern of thought and behavior is known as a(n) ________.",
    back: "personality"
  },
  {
    id: "R111",
    front: "In Milgram's controversial study on obedience, nearly ________ of the participants were willing to administer what appeared to be lethal electrical shocks to another person because they were told to do so by an authority figure.",
    back: "2/3"
  },
  {
    id: "R112",
    front: "A researcher interested in what factors make an employee best suited for a given job would most likely identify as a(n) ________ psychologist.",
    back: "I-O (Industrial-Organizational)"
  },
  {
    id: "R113",
    front: "If someone wanted to become a psychology professor at a 4-year college, then s/he would probably need a ________ degree in psychology.",
    back: "PhD"
  },
  {
    id: "R114",
    front: "The ________ places less emphasis on research and more emphasis on application of therapeutic skills.",
    back: "PsyD"
  },
  {
    id: "R115",
    front: "Which of the following degrees would be the minimum required to teach psychology courses in high school?",
    back: "bachelor's degree"
  },
  {
    id: "R116",
    front: "One would need at least a(n) ________ degree to serve as a school psychologist.",
    back: "master's"
  },
];